voyagersopris.com 2015-06-12

# Privacy | Voyager Sopris

We take your privacy and security seriously. We do not sell, rent, or share your personal information with anyone else. However, because we do gather certain types of information about visitors to our website, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of this information. This privacy statement outlines what information we gather, why we gather it, and how you can easily opt in or opt out of our special services.

**Customer contact information:**  
We use customer contact information from our order form and subscriber services’ registration form, such as your name, address, school, phone number, and e-mail address, to help us ship and track your orders accurately and efficiently. We may use your phone number or e-mail address to contact you in case we have questions about your order.

**Disclaimer statement:**

Voyager Sopris Learning, its employees, and its authors make no representations, and assume no liability, legal or otherwise, for the accuracy, reliability, applicability, use, or misuse of the information and strategies described on this website or in its publications. Information on this website or in Voyager Sopris Learning’s publications is not intended to replace professional judgment in determining and implementing the best course of action for individual students and are described to illustrate possible strategies previously used by other professionals.

**Secure online ordering:**  
Voyager Sopris is a member in good standing of VeriSign, Inc., a leading provider of Internet Trust Services. The Trust Certificate issued to Cambium Learning from VeriSign, Inc., confirms our ability to conduct trusted and secure electronic commerce and communications over IP networks. Voyager Sopris uses SSL (Secure Socket Layer) technology, an industry-standard protocol used to establish secure communications between a web server and a client. We also currently support 128-bit encryption—the most secure way to protect your credit card information. To further maintain your security, we delete your credit card information after each transaction rather than store it in our database.

**Opt-in services:**  
We use information collected from the registration forms for special services; to help us customize our web services to best meet your needs; and to provide you with occasional updates about discounts, special product introductions, and free resources related to education.

**Opt-out services:**  
You may refuse further communications from us at any time. To opt out of an e-mail service, simply select “unsubscribe” at the bottom of the e-mail and you will be promptly removed. If you have any questions or concerns, please contact [**customerservice@cambiumlearning.com**](mailto:customerservice@cambiumlearning.com).

**Questionnaires** :  
From time to time, Voyager Sopris may conduct voluntary online questionnaires to help us better serve you and to help us develop products that address your specific needs. If you choose to participate in these questionnaires, they may be completed online, mailed to us, or faxed to us, whichever you prefer.

**“Cookies:”**  
“Cookies” are small text files that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies to remember your personal information so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. Cookies also allow you to store products in your cart without purchasing them. This allows you to leave the site and return later to purchase the items in your cart, if you choose.

**We’ll update you if we ever make changes to our policy:**  
Voyager Sopris may modify, add, or remove sections of our Privacy Policy by updating the terms described on this web page. Any changes will be posted to this page, and these changes will become effective immediately upon posting. Your continued use of the site following the changes constitutes your consent of our Privacy and Security Policy.

**Links to other sites:**  
When you travel to other sites from the Voyager Sopris site, be aware that these outside sites may collect and use your personal information. We cannot accept responsibility or liability for the privacy practices of other companies or individuals with links to and from our site.

Note: Any updated policies will be posted to the service immediately.
